[
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a633463383235363431663761336237646638393939313437616139643637393339646664656362653134326165666238386532383162356538656439613565302c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303738343236312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766685059,
        "question": "Will Spotify's top song on December 25 be 'All I Want For Christmas Is You'?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a363865636466656561343037323135346232653230626665616164346437396237353033356238323565383865386236393464373765663438393334306665392c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303736353234362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766642551,
        "question": "Will Trump say \"Very Merry Christmas\" this week? (December 22 - 28)",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a343832666437633737383935323966376131386231646232373165316134333734643865363365666436613838303436383530316230333936656161666434372c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303735323338362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766623417,
        "question": "Kodiak FDV above $50M one day after launch?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a646266623030383365613838663837373531663736346366663334666539343038373432663534353566616233643661313436316333616533663265613861372c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303734373931362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766614921,
        "question": "Will MrBeast's next video get less than 60 million views on week 1?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a316561376132346563653436363637386339393931333262636638626135633033643435613561396330666638393338326466323235313262616330313235342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303734323836392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766604883,
        "question": "Julius Randle: Assists Over 4.5",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a353562323766333964656664636235363563373062613039633461306564333837343338666232333161313935663238333463306638633237336539323130362c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733373037392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766593343,
        "question": "Desmond Bane: Assists Over 4.5",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a643961636461386635323830636537313831363566343633613765363633346234376334356432346435353931373337316632336238623936316263643661632c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733343334312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766585317,
        "question": "Will 'A Minecraft Movie' have the second best domestic opening weekend in 2025?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a396437346534623765656537373032346535303538336536393261363937633236316233363036613165363961393536616134366532663336386533633936362c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733333036392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766582401,
        "question": "Epstein blackmail evidence released by March 31?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a623133666435343431633333333636333765663163353966356236363534306638303561333866363765363231326263323562363139663965616635613239352c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733313631382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766582213,
        "question": "Epstein blackmail evidence released in 2025?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a396437346534623765656537373032346535303538336536393261363937633236316233363036613165363961393536616134366532663336386533633936362c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733313534352c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766579419,
        "question": "Epstein blackmail evidence released by March 31?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a623133666435343431633333333636333765663163353966356236363534306638303561333866363765363231326263323562363139663965616635613239352c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733313434332c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766579399,
        "question": "Epstein blackmail evidence released in 2025?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a323862303465336331633239323635303839343263636462353636386464623739363335666563633263383661613961663262303330623036326232663431312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303733303738372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766579861,
        "question": "Games Total: O/U 2.5",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a373261626364613064653932356561633038323737363465323536643633393530363138333939633565343063356363346161336336386134656133656561642c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303732333234372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766565653,
        "question": "Will the highest temperature in Seattle be 52Â°F or higher on December 23?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a663831633430363166386638376164626432623465326364313964653963356139376139373933623632303361646530623637313362306566396464653365312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303731363932312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766552985,
        "question": "Will Red Star FC win on 2025-12-05?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a386436353931613936636363623732316434663230393733376138633665663532373630373537303062346161636631333965383237653335303865393038332c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38303730353234362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1766524703,
        "question": "Fact Check: Epstein video confirmed real?",
        "answer": "P4"
    }
]
